Syed Hussain Raza

SOFTWARE ENGINEER · COMPUTER SCIENCE MAJOR · UNIVERSITY OF WATERLOO

• 226-792-8796 | • sh5raza@uwaterloo.ca | • https://www.linkedin.com/in/hussainr565/

About Me

 $\textbf{Blockchain:} \ DApps \cdot Solidity \cdot Web3.js \cdot Truffle \cdot Ethereum \cdot Metamask \cdot Remix \ IDE \cdot Cryptocurrencies \cdot Hardhat$

Programming: C++/C# · Python · JavaScript · HTML/CSS

Experience with: React.js · SQL · Smart Contract Development · Django · Panda

Experience

Blimphomes: Full Stack Developer

May. 2022 - Aug. 2022 | Toronto, CA

- Worked in Web Application Development in React JS Environment.
- Utilized Django and Panda for creating and maintaining applications.

Canadian Automobile Association: Developer

May. 2021 - Dec. 2021 | Toronto, CA

Worked on revamping a regression automation project for the company. The main objective was to improve execution time and change from the recording to the modular architecture.

Manulife Financial: Salesforce Engineer (Services)

Sep. 2020 - Dec. 2020 | Waterloo, CA

Developed a Lightning web application where customers can post their feedback. The good ideas are developed, delivered and rewarded at development stage. Additions can be made to the ideas through comment functionality.

Manulife Financial: Salesforce Engineer (Platform)

Jan. 2020 - May. 2020 | Waterloo, CA

Data Migration Tool: A React application that migrates test data from lower-level environments to higher-level ones since test data is removed from Sandboxes after a sandbox refresh. Before this application, test data was manually migrated, which was time-consuming and arduous.

Allstream: Application Developer

May. 2019 - Aug. 2019 | Mississauga, CA

Developed Lightning web components as part of the Salesforce Migration from Classic to the lightning environment.

Certifications

BTA Certified Blockchain Developer - Ethereum

Jan. 2022 Jan. 2022

BTA Certified Blockchain Solution Architect

IBM Blockchain Essentials

Jan. 2022

Education

University of Waterloo

Sep. 2018 - April. 2023 | Waterloo, CA

HONOURS BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE